we will be talking about self-interested
我们将谈论自私的
agents and their interactions
代理及其互动
so let's first speak about what we mean
所以我们先说说我们的意思
by self-interested agents we don't mean
对于自私的经纪人，我们并不是说
necessarily that agents are adversarial
必然是代理商具有对抗性
or don't care about what happened to
或不在乎发生了什么
other agents what we mean by that is
其他代理商，我们的意思是
that agents have opinions have
代理商有意见
preferences and so there's some
偏好，所以有一些
description of the world how the world
世界的描述世界如何
could be and in different descriptions
可能是并且在不同的描述中
the agents have different preferences
代理商有不同的偏好
and different utilities as we'll say and
以及我们将要说的不同的实用程序
so what we mean by utility function is a
所以我们所说的效用函数是
mathematical measure that tells you how
告诉你如何的数学测量
much the agents likes or does not like a
代理商非常喜欢或不喜欢
given situation
给定情况
it describes not only their attitude
它不仅描述了他们的态度
towards a definite of events so for
对于一定的事件，所以
example tomorrow the temperature will be
明天的温度将是
exactly 25 degrees centigrade but but in
正好25摄氏度，但
fact it will describe the preferences
实际上它将描述偏好
towards a distribution of such outcomes
分配这样的结果
so it really captures their attitude
所以这真的抓住了他们的态度
towards uncertainty about events so for
对事件的不确定性
example if I tell you that it will be 25
例如，如果我告诉你它将是25
degrees with probability 0.7 and 24
度为0.7和24
degrees with probability 0.3 you might
度，概率为0.3，您可能
have an opinion about how much you like
对你喜欢多少有意见
that versus some other distribution and
与其他发行版相比，
the decision theoretic approach which is
决策理论方法是
what underlies modern game theory says
现代博弈论的基础是什么
that you're going to try to act in the
你将要尝试采取行动
way that maximizes your expected or
最大化您的预期或
average utility and so this is a concept
平均效用，所以这是一个概念
we need to get comfortable with and and
我们需要对and和
it's not obvious that one would want to
人们是否愿意
use such an approach so for example we
使用这种方法，例如
are going to look at a single dimension
将要看一个单一的维度
so your preferences will
所以你的喜好会
all beyond a scale as we'll see the
一切都超出规模，我们将看到
scale that is not that important unlike
规模不那么重要
probabilities utilities don't have to
概率实用程序不必
lie in the 0-1 scale but they will lie
说谎在0-1规模，但他们会说谎
on a linear dimension and maybe maybe
在线性维度上，也许
that's inappropriate or for example you
那是不合适的，例如你
might have some level of wealth and some
可能有一定程度的财富和一些
degree of health and for a certain level
健康程度和一定水平
of of each one you'll have some some
每一个中，您都会有一些
some some notion of well-being but is it
一些关于幸福的概念，但这是
appropriate to put the two together and
适合将两者放在一起
have a single scale you might you might
有一个单一的规模，你可能会
question that similarly why is looking
同样为什么要看的问题
at the expected value when you're
当您处于期望值时
looking at your uncertainty while
看着你的不确定性
looking at the expected value an
看期望值
appropriate way to capture your attitude
捕捉态度的适当方法
and so these are not trivial statements
所以这些不是琐碎的陈述
and in fact are not tautological they
而且实际上不是重言式的
make a subjective claim but there's a
提出主观主张，但有一个
very long tradition and maybe the most
悠久的传统，也许是最悠久的
famous reference is to phenomena
著名的参考是现象
Morgenstern simul book on on which is
Morgenstern simul上的书是
really in some ways the introduction to
确实在某种程度上介绍了
modern day in game theory that derives
博弈论中的现代派生
the these utility function from more
这些实用功能更多
basic assumptions one makes and we won't
一个基本假设，我们不会
go into that but we just wanted to flag
进入那个，但是我们只想标记
this issue as something that will
这个问题会
underlie everything we say about game
成为我们谈论游戏的基础
theory and which really underlies one
理论，这实际上是一个基础
game theory
博弈论